Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
ABOUT ENDLESSNESS
It's September already.
Mm...
I saw a man...
...who wanted to surprise his wife
with a nice dinner.
I need to tell you something.
When I walked up
these stairs last Friday...
...someone was walking behind me.
I turned around
and realised it was Sverker Olsson.
An old schoolmate I haven't seen in...
...well, years.
So I said "Hi, Sverker.
It's been a long time."
"How are things?"
He didn't answer.
He just walked by without saying a word.
Then I realised why.
I'd hurt him once, badly.
And he hadn't forgotten.
Oh, hi, Sverker.
It's been a long time.
I saw a man...
...with his mind elsewhere.
I saw a woman,
a communications manager,
incapable of feeling shame.
I saw a man...
...who did not trust banks...
...and so he kept his savings
in his mattress.
Crucify! Crucify!
Get up!
Get up, you scumbag!
Crucify! Crucify!
What have I done wrong?
Stand up!
Come on!
Crucify! Crucify!
They drove nails through my hands.
What now?
It's gone now.
They drove nails through my hands.
I saw a young man...
...who had not yet found love.
There's nothing strange
about having nightmares.
We all have them sometimes.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
I've had many patients with
all kinds of nightmares.
But I don't think
I've encountered this one before.
Not the most pleasant dream,
I must say.
No...
And recurring too, I understand?
Yes.
You are obviously burdened by something.
Any idea what might have triggered it?
Yes...
It was when I began losing faith.
Faith in the existence of God.
Oh my.
You're a priest, right?
Yes, it's my livelihood.
It's my job to preach about God.
Without believing in what you're saying.
That's not a pleasant situation,
I must say.
No...
But... could it be...
...God doesn't actually exist?
No, that would be terrible.
What's there to believe in then?
Damned if I know.
Maybe be content with being alive.
That's how I look at it.
We will try to help you with your troubles.
But as I'm sure you already know,
I don't work for free.
And neither do you, right?
No...
I suggest we meet one week from now.
Same time, here at my office.
Ingrid has all your information.
As I said, I suggest we meet here,
one week from now,
and help you with this.
And I would like to thank you
for coming here.
Ingrid will see you out.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I saw a man...
...who had stepped on a landmine...
...and lost his legs.
And it made him very sad.
Over here.
Wave to grandma.
Up you go!
Hello!
Wave to grandma.
My God, my God!
Why have you forsaken me?
The body of Christ
broken for you.
The blood of Christ
shed for you.
The body of Christ
broken for you.
The blood of Christ
shed for you.
I saw a man...
...who had lost his faith.
The body of Christ
broken for you.
The blood of Christ
shed for you.
The body of Christ
broken for you.
The blood of Christ
shed for you.
I saw two parents...
...who had lost their son in a war.
Tommy, dearest.
Dad is just fetching some water.
He'll be right back.
We're making the plot look nice
for you, Tommy.
You should know that, Tommy.
We're always making it look nice.
So you don't have to be embarrassed.
We're thinking of you, every day.
Yes, Tommy. Mommy's darling. We do.
Yes, we do.
I saw a couple,
two lovers...
...floating above a city,
renowned for its beauty,
but now in ruins.
- There! Daddy!
- Hi honey. Hi!
I've missed you so.
I saw a woman...
...who thought
no one was waiting for her.
I saw a woman...
...who loved champagne.
So much. So much.
Pardon me, is your name
possibly Lisa Larsson?
No, I'm sorry.
I saw a man...
...who had lost his way.
No.
- Please...
- No.
No, no, no, no...
- No!
No...
Please, please...
Please. No, no, no.
No. Please...
No! No, no, no!
Please. No, no, no...
I saw a man...
...begging for his life.
Please. No.
No...
No! No! No!
Please...
Come on, guys!
I saw a woman...
...who had problems with her shoe.
I saw a man...
...who wanted to protect
his family's honour...
...and changed his mind.
I could see the two of you
had a lot to talk about.
No, what?
I could see the two of you
had a lot to talk about!
Calm down! Calm down!
You do know that I love you?
Yes dear, I know. I know.
I know, I know.
The first law of thermodynamics...
...states that...
...everything is energy...
...and it can never be destroyed.
It is endless.
It can only change...
...from one form to another.
That means...
...you are energy,
I am energy.
And that your energy...
...and my energy...
...can never cease to exist.
It can only transform...
...into something new.
Theoretically our energies...
...can meet again...
...in millions of years.
And then,
maybe you're a potato...
...or a tomato.
Then I'd rather be a tomato.
I saw a man...
...who wanted to conquer the world...
...and realised he would fail.
Sieg Heil!
I don't know what I want.
Excuse me?
Poor bastard.
What?
You're not allowed to be sad anymore?
Of course. But why can't he be sad
at home instead?
Why here?
I saw a man with his daughter...
...on their way to a birthday party.
And it rained.
It rained a lot.
Hello!
What should I do now
that I have lost my faith?
I'm sorry,
but we're just about to close.
What should I do now
that I have lost my faith?
I have to talk to doctor Lindh.
That's not possible. We're just about
to close and doctor Lindh is going home.
Please.
Hello.
What should I do now
that I have lost my faith?
I'm sorry, but we're closing now.
And you have an appointment next week.
I have a bus to catch.
I'm sorry, but I have to catch my bus.
What should I do now
that I have lost my faith?
Well, we're closing now.
We're closing the office, so...
- What should I do?
- You can talk about it next week.
- No, no...
- I have to ask you to leave now.
What should I do...
I have a bus to catch.
No...
What should I do now
that I have lost my faith?
What should I do...
- I'd better not miss my bus.
- He'll probably leave soon.
What should I do now
that I have lost my faith?
Pardon me.
- Torbjörn.
- Hasse.
- I understand you've got a toothache.
- Yes.
Well, that's no laughing matter.
Open wide.
Ow, ow!
That's the one causing you grief.
- I think we need some local anaesthesia.
- No, no. I'm so scared of needles.
We'll have to make do without then.
Ow!
Goodbye.
My sincere apologies.
The doctor is in a bad mood today.
He's got problems.
Oh, really?
Isn't it quite fantastic?
What?
Everything.
Everything is fantastic.
Well, yes.
- I think so, at least.
- Alright.
I think so, at least.
Okay, then.
I saw a defeated army...
...marching to the prison camps...
...in Siberia.
Well, hello.
I guess you're getting tired of hearing
about Sverker Olsson again.
My old mate from school I ran into
a few weeks back.
This Friday it happened again.
And he didn't say hello this time either.
- What's he up to these days?
- I wouldn't know.
But I hear he got himself
a PhD, somehow.
He certainly wasn't too bright in school.
But now he's got his degree.
And that's more than I've got.
But dear,
you've done so many other things.
I'm not so sure about that.
I think time is rushing by,
and I haven't accomplished anything.
Now you're exaggerating.
- We travelled, and saw Niagara Falls.
- Yeah, yeah.
- And the Leaning Tower of Pisa.
- Well, yes.
And last year you climbed
the stairs of the Eiffel Tower
with your bad knee.
I'm sure Sverker Olsson
has been there too.
I can't believe a loser like
Sverker Olsson got a PhD.
It's really quite annoying.
But why do you keep dwelling on that?
It's annoying.
- It's annoying.
- Yeah, yeah.
I saw a man...
...who had problems with his car.